Finding Aid to The Georgia O'Keeffe Foundation Photographs MS.57
Georgia O'Keeffe Museum
- Georgia O'Keeffe, 1977; 2006.6.798; 1 Photographic Prints black and white photograph 7 x 4 15/16 inches; Stamp of College of Santa Fe on verso. Staple holes in upper left corner. Handwritten on verso: A-35 12-77 Georgia O'KeeffeHandwritten on verso: "NEW MEXICO 3", "A-35", "12-77 Georgia O'Keeffe" Stamp on verso: "PLEASE CREDIT COLLEGE OF SANTA FE PHOTO" printed on verso: "THIS PAPER IS MANUFACTURED BY KODAK"
- Georgia O'Keeffe, 1977; 2006.6.799; 1 Photographic Prints black and white photograph 7 x 4 15/16 inches; Stamp of College of Santa Fe on verso. Staple holes in upper left corner. Handwritten on verso: D-8 12-77 Georgia O'KeeffeHandwritten on verso: "NEW MEXICO 11", "D-8 12-77 Georgia O'Keeffe" Stamp on verso: "PLEASE CREDIT COLLEGE OF SANTA FE PHOTO" printed on verso: "THIS PAPER IS MANUFACTURED BY KODAK"
- Georgia O'Keeffe, 1977; 2006.6.800; 1 Photographic Prints black and white photograph 7 x 4 15/16 inches; Stamp of College of Santa Fe on verso. Staple holes in upper left corner. Handwritten on verso: A-5 12-77 Georgia O'KeeffeHandwritten on verso: "NEW MEXICO 2", "A-5 12-77 Georgia O'Keeffe" Stamp on verso: "PLEASE CREDIT COLLEGE OF SANTA FE PHOTO" printed on verso: "THIS PAPER IS MANUFACTURED BY KODAK"
- Georgia O'Keeffe, 1977; 2006.6.801; 1 Photographic Prints black and white photograph 6 15/16 x 4 15/16 inches; Stamp of College of Santa Fe on verso. Staple holes in upper left corner. Handwritten on verso: A-36 Georgia O'Keeffe 12-77Handwritten on verso: "NEW MEXICO 4", "A-36", "12-77 Georgia O'Keeffe" Stamp on verso: "PLEASE CREDIT COLLEGE OF SANTA FE PHOTO" printed on verso: "THIS PAPER IS MANUFACTURED BY KODAK"
- Georgia O'Keeffe, 1977; 2006.6.802; 1 Photographic Prints black and white photograph 6 15/16 x 4 15/16 inches; Stamp of College of Santa Fe on verso. Staple holes in upper left corner. Handwritten on verso: B-4 12-77 Georgia O'KeeffeHandwritten on verso: "NEW MEXICO 5", "B-4 12-77 Georgia O'Keeffe" Stamp on verso: "PLEASE CREDIT COLLEGE OF SANTA FE PHOTO" printed on verso: "THIS PAPER IS MANUFACTURED BY KODAK"
- Georgia O'Keeffe, 1977; 2006.6.803; 1 Photographic Prints black and white photograph 6 15/16 x 4 15/16 inches; Stamp of College of Santa Fe on verso. Staple holes in upper left corner. Handwritten on verso: B-15 12-77 Georgia O'KeeffeHandwritten on verso: "NEW MEXICO 6", "B-15 12-77 Georgia O'Keeffe" Stamp on verso: "PLEASE CREDIT COLLEGE OF SANTA FE PHOTO" printed on verso: "THIS PAPER IS MANUFACTURED BY KODAK"
- Georgia O'Keeffe, 1977; 2006.6.804; 1 Photographic Prints black and white photograph 7 1/16 x 5 inches; Stamp of College of Santa Fe on verso. Staple holes in upper left corner. Handwritten on verso: C-31A Georgia O'Keefe 12-77Handwritten on verso: "NEW MEXICO 9", "C-31A", "12-77 Georgia O'Keeffe" Stamp on verso: "PLEASE CREDIT COLLEGE OF SANTA FE PHOTO" printed on verso: "THIS PAPER IS MANUFACTURED BY KODAK"
- Georgia O'Keeffe with Eleanor Capanigro, 1977; 2006.6.805; 1 Photographic Prints black and white photograph 6 13/16 x 5 inches; Stamp of College of Santa Fe on verso. Staple holes in the upper left corner. Handwritten on verso: B-37 12-77 Georgia O'keeffeHandwritten on verso: "NEW MEXICO 8", "B-37", "12-77 Georgia O'Keeffe" Stamp on verso: "PLEASE CREDIT COLLEGE OF SANTA FE PHOTO" printed on verso: "THIS PAPER IS MANUFACTURED BY KODAK"
- Georgia O'Keeffe with Eleanor Capanigro, 1977; 2006.6.806; 1 Photographic Prints black and white photograph 4 15/16 x 7 1/8 inches; Stamp of College of Santa Fe on verso. Staple holes in lower left corner. Handwritten on verso:12-77 D-27 Georgia O'KeefeHandwritten on verso: "NEW MEXICO 14", "D-28", "12-77 Georgia O'Keeffe" Stamp on verso: "PLEASE CREDIT COLLEGE OF SANTA FE PHOTO" printed on verso: "THIS PAPER IS MANUFACTURED BY KODAK"
- Georgia O'Keeffe with Eleanor Capanigro, 1977; 2006.6.807; 1 Photographic Prints black and white photograph 5 x 7 1/16 inches; Stamp of College of Santa Fe on verso. Staple holes in lower left corner. Handwritten on verso: D-28 12-77 Georgia O'KeeffeHandwritten on verso: "NEW MEXICO 13", "12-77 D/27Georgia O'Keeffe" Stamp on verso: "PLEASE CREDIT COLLEGE OF SANTA FE PHOTO" printed on verso: "THIS PAPER IS MANUFACTURED BY KODAK"
- Georgia O'Keeffe with Eleanor Capanigro, 1977; 2006.6.808; 1 Photographic Prints black and white photograph 4 7/8 x 7 1/16 inches; Stamp of College of Santa Fe on verso. Staple holes in lower left corner. Handwritten on verso: B-26 12-77 Georgia O'keeffeHandwritten on verso: "B-25", "12-77 Georgia O'Keeffe", "NEW MEXICO 7" Stamp on verso: "PLEASE CREDIT COLLEGE OF SANTA FE PHOTO" printed on verso: "THIS PAPER IS MANUFACTURED BY KODAK"
- Georgia O'Keeffe with Josefita Pino (Fita), circa 1980s; 2006.6.809; 1 Photographic Prints color photograph 3 1/2 x 4 7/8 inches
- Georgia O'Keeffe, circa 1976-1981; 2006.6.810; 1 Photographic Prints color photograph 3 3/8 x 5 inches; Kodak stamp on verso 1976. Staple holes in upper left cornerstamp on verso: Kodak Aug. 1976; handwritten on verso: "5",
- Georgia O'Keeffe, circa 1976-1981; 2006.6.811; 1 Photographic Prints color photograph 7 15/16 x 11 15/16 inches; Stamp on verso 1981stamp on verso: Kodak Jan 81
- Georgia O'Keeffe with Juan Hamilton and Agapita Judy Lopez, 1982; 2006.6.812; 1 Photographic Prints color photograph 3 1/2 x 4 3/8 inches; Soft focus. Digital writing on verso: 10/82Digital writing on verso: "10/82"
- Georgia O'Keeffe with Juan Hamilton and Agapita Judy Lopez, 1982; 2006.6.813; 1 Photographic Prints color photograph 3 1/2 x 4 3/8 inches; Soft focus. Digital writing on verso: 10/82Digital writing on verso: "10/82"
- Georgia O'Keeffe with Juan Hamilton and Agapita Judy Lopez, 1982; 2006.6.814; 1 Photographic Prints color photograph 3 1/2 x 4 3/8 inches; Soft focus.
- Georgia O'Keeffe with Juan Hamilton and Agapita Judy Lopez, 1982; 2006.6.815; 1 Photographic Prints color photograph 3 1/2 x 4 5/16 inches; Soft focus.
- Georgia O'Keeffe with Juan Hamilton, 1982; 2006.6.816; 1 Photographic Prints color photograph 3 1/2 x 4 3/8 inches
- Georgia O'Keeffe with Juan Hamilton, 1982; 2006.6.817; 1 Photographic Prints color photograph 3 1/2 x 4 3/8 inches
- Juan Hamilton, 1982; 2006.6.818; 1 Photographic Prints color photograph 3 1/2 x 4 7/16 inches
- Georgia O'Keeffe Among Chamisa, circa 1960s; 2006.6.819; 1 Photographic Prints black and white photograph 3 1/2 x 4 1/4 inches; Framed. Letters stamped on verso: B427451ELStamp on verso: B427451EL
- Georgia O'Keeffe Sitting on Stone Bench, circa 1950s; 2006.6.820; 1 Photographic Prints black and white photograph 3 3/8 x 3 1/2 inches
- Georgia O'Keeffe Sitting on Stone Bench, circa 1950s; 2006.6.821; 1 Photographic Prints black and white photograph 3 7/16 x 3 3/8 inches; Note on verso: drawn from Wickham Moore file (early letters) pictures date from early 1950'sPost-it on verso: "drawn from Wickham Moore file (early letters) pictures date from early 1950's" Stamp on verso: "KODAK VELOX PAPER"
- Georgia O'Keeffe Among Trees, circa 1950s; 2006.6.822; 1 Photographic Prints black and white photograph 3 7/16 x 3 3/8 inches; Stamp on verso: "F25805"
- Georgia O'Keeffe Among Trees, circa 1950s; 2006.6.823; 1 Photographic Prints black and white photograph 3 1/2 x 3 1/2 inches; Framed.
- Georgia O'Keeffe with Governor Knowles, 1966; 2006.6.824; 1 Photographic Prints black and white photograph 7 15/16 x 9 15/16 inches; Handwritten on verso: Georgia O'Keeffe with Gov. Knowles (illegible)Handwritten on verso: "Georgia O Keeeffe and Gov. Knowles"
  Governor Warren Knowles and Georgia O'Keeffe at the presentation of Wisconsin Governor's award for Creativity in the Arts (http://www.wisconsinhistory.org/Content.aspx?dsNav=Nrc:id-5,N:4294963828-4294955414&dsNavOnly=N:1135&dsRecordDetails=R:IM115812)
- Georgia O'Keeffe with Governor Knowles, 1966; 2006.6.825; 1 Photographic Prints black and white photograph 8 x 10 inches
- Georgia O'Keeffe, 1971; 2006.6.844; Langton, Basil, 1912-2003; 1 Photographic Prints copy print 13 13/16 x 11 inches; Stamp and label on verso of Basil Langton, 1971. Handwritten on verso: "LANGTON 1" "71" Label on verso: "GEORGIA O'KEEFFE 1971 GHOST RANCH ABIQUIU N.M. USA Photograph by Basil Langton" "PHOTO RESEARCHERS INC. 60 East 56th Street, New York, N.Y. 10022" "Basil Langton 855 10th St., #208 Santa Monica, CA 90403" Stamp on verso: "19__ Basil Langton. This photograph cannot be copied, televised, reproduced, or used in any form without the express and written permission of, Basil Langton: 41 W. 69th St. New York, N.Y. 10023" "219 S. EARNNSTON AVE. LOS ANGELES, CALF 90010" scratched out "ALL RIGHTS RESERVED"
  Profile headshot portrait of O'Keeffe wearing a Marimekko patterned dress, hair pulled back looking to viewer right.
- Georgia O'Keeffe, 1980; 2006.6.845; Pritzlaff, Richard G., 1902-1997; 1 Photographic Prints color photograph 13 15/16 x 10 15/16 inches
  Georgia O'Keeffe at Sapello Ranch.
- Georgia O'Keeffe, 1980; 2006.6.846; Pritzlaff, Richard G., 1902-1997; 1 Photographic Prints color photograph 13 15/16 x 10 15/16 inches
- Georgia O'Keeffe, 1980; 2006.6.847; Pritzlaff, Richard G., 1902-1997; 1 Photographic Prints color photograph 13 15/16 x 10 15/16 inches
- Georgia O'Keeffe and Alfred Stieglitz at An American Place (contact sheet), circa 1946; 2006.6.861; 1 Photographic Prints contact sheet 9 15/16 x 8 1/8 inches; Handwritten on verso: "2018", "Cecil Beaton", "Return to O'Keeffe", "2019" (circled)
- Georgia O'Keeffe and Alfred Stieglitz at An American Place (contact sheet), circa 1946; 2006.6.862; 1 Photographic Prints contact sheet 9 15/16 x 8 1/8 inches; Handwritten on verso: "2018"(circled), "Cecil Beaton", "Return to O'Keeffe", "2019", "11995-U-10"
- Georgia O'Keeffe, circa 1949-circa 1977; 2006.6.863; Bry, Doris, 1920-2014; 1 Photographic Prints black and white photograph 6 15/16 x 4 15/16 inches
- Georgia O'Keeffe, circa 1949-circa 1977; 2006.6.864; Bry, Doris, 1920-2014; 1 Photographic Prints black and white photograph 6 15/16 x 4 15/16 inches
- Georgia O'Keeffe, circa 1949-circa 1977; 2006.6.865; Bry, Doris, 1920-2014; 1 Photographic Prints black and white photograph 7 x 5 inches
- Georgia O'Keeffe, circa 1949-circa 1977; 2006.6.866; Bry, Doris, 1920-2014; 1 Photographic Prints black and white photograph 7 x 5 inches; Handwritten on verso: "?"
- Georgia O'Keeffe, circa 1949-circa 1977; 2006.6.867; Bry, Doris, 1920-2014; 1 Photographic Prints black and white photograph 7 x 4 15/16 inches
- Georgia O'Keeffe, circa 1949-circa 1977; 2006.6.868; Bry, Doris, 1920-2014; 1 Photographic Prints black and white photograph 7 1/16 x 4 15/16 inches
- Georgia O'Keeffe, circa 1949-circa 1977; 2006.6.869; Bry, Doris, 1920-2014; 1 Photographic Prints black and white photograph 7 x 4 15/16 inches
- Georgia O'Keeffe, circa 1949-circa 1977; 2006.6.870; Bry, Doris, 1920-2014; 1 Photographic Prints black and white photograph 6 15/16 x 4 15/16 inches
- Georgia O'Keeffe, circa 1949-circa 1977; 2006.6.871; Bry, Doris, 1920-2014; 1 Photographic Prints black and white photograph 7 x 4 15/16 inches
- Georgia O'Keeffe, circa 1949-circa 1977; 2006.6.872; Bry, Doris, 1920-2014; 1 Photographic Prints black and white photograph 7 x 5 inches
- Georgia O'Keeffe, circa 1949-circa 1977; 2006.6.873; Bry, Doris, 1920-2014; 1 Photographic Prints black and white photograph 7 x 4 7/8 inches
- Georgia O'Keeffe, circa 1949-circa 1977; 2006.6.874; Bry, Doris, 1920-2014; 1 Photographic Prints black and white photograph 7 x 5 1/16 inches
- Georgia O'Keeffe, circa 1949-circa 1977; 2006.6.875; Bry, Doris, 1920-2014; 1 Photographic Prints black and white photograph 7 x 4 15/16 inches
- Georgia O'Keeffe, circa 1949-circa 1977; 2006.6.876; Bry, Doris, 1920-2014; 1 Photographic Prints black and white photograph 7 x 5 1/16 inches
- Georgia O'Keeffe, circa 1949-circa 1977; 2006.6.877; Bry, Doris, 1920-2014; 1 Photographic Prints black and white photograph 7 1/16 x 5 inches
- Georgia O'Keeffe, circa 1949-circa 1977; 2006.6.878; Bry, Doris, 1920-2014; 1 Photographic Prints black and white photograph 7 x 5 inches
- Georgia O'Keeffe, circa 1950; 2006.6.879; Bry, Doris, 1920-2014; 1 Photographic Prints black and white photograph 6 7/8 x 4 7/8 inches; Handwritten on verso: Kindly return to Georgia O'Keeffe Abiquiu New Mexico. Photo by Doris BryHandwritten on verso: "BRY 31a", "Kindly return to Georgia O'Keeffe ABIQUIU New Mexico photo by Doris Bry" (in Georgia O'Keeffe's handwriting)
- Georgia O'Keeffe with Chows, 1972; 2006.6.880; Bry, Doris, 1920-2014; 1 Photographic Prints black and white photograph 7 15/16 x 10 inches; Handwritten on verso; Stamp of Doris Bry on verso; Handwritten on verso: 523 1388 C1-0; most likely JingoStamp on verso: "Please credit photograph to:", "DORIS BRY 11 EAST 73rd St. NEW YORK, N. Y. 10021" Handwritten on verso: "523 1388 C1-0 2"
- Georgia O'Keeffe with Chows, 1972; 2006.6.881; Bry, Doris, 1920-2014; 1 Photographic Prints black and white photograph 9 7/8 x 8 1/16 inches; Handwritten on verso; Stamp of Doris Bry on verso; Handwritten on verso: 5231388 C1-6Stamp on verso: "Please credit photograph to:", "DORIS BRY 11 EAST 73rd St. NEW YORK, N. Y. 10021" Handwritten on verso: "523 1388 C1-6 4"
- Georgia O'Keeffe with Chows, 1972; 2006.6.882; Bry, Doris, 1920-2014; 1 Photographic Prints black and white photograph 9 7/8 x 8 1/16 inches; Handwritten on verso; Stamp of Doris Bry on verso; most likely JingoStamp on verso: "Please credit photograph to:", "DORIS BRY 11 EAST 73rd St. NEW YORK, N. Y. 10021" Handwritten on verso: "523 1368 C1-7 4"
- Georgia O'Keeffe with Chows, circa 1970s; 2006.6.883; Bry, Doris, 1920-2014; 1 Photographic Prints black and white photograph 9 7/8 x 8 1/16 inches; Handwritten on verso; Stamp of Doris Bry on verso; most likely JingoStamp on verso: "Please credit photograph to:", "DORIS BRY 11 EAST 73rd St. NEW YORK, N. Y. 10021" Handwritten on verso: "523 1388 C2-8 2"
- Georgia O'Keeffe with Chow, after 1952; 2006.6.884; Bry, Doris, 1920-2014; 1 Photographic Prints black and white photograph 2 13/16 x 4 7/16 inches; Handwritten on verso: by D Bry from 35mm colorHandwritten on verso: "by D. Bry -From 35 mm color"
- Georgia O'Keeffe with Chow, after 1952; 2006.6.885; Bry, Doris, 1920-2014; 1 Photographic Prints black and white photograph 2 13/16 x 4 3/8 inches; Handwritten on verso: by D Bry from 35mm colorHandwritten on verso: "by D. Bry -From 35 mm color"
- Georgia O'Keeffe with Chow, 1972; 2006.6.886; Bry, Doris, 1920-2014; 1 Photographic Prints color photograph 3 x 5 1/16 inches; Handwritten on verso:from DB 11/1972; JingoStamp on verso: Kodak Dec 72; Handwritten on verso: from DB 11/1972
- Georgia O'Keeffe at Lake Powell, circa 1970s; 2006.6.887; Bry, Doris, 1920-2014; 1 Photographic Prints black and white photograph 7 1/16 x 5 inches; Handwritten on verso:"BRY 1", "5-2", "5-2", "MSH OK" (?)
- Georgia O'Keeffe at Lake Powell, circa 1970s; 2006.6.888; Bry, Doris, 1920-2014; 1 Photographic Prints black and white photograph 7 15/16 x 9 15/16 inches; Handwritten on verso; Stamp of Doris Bry on versoStamp on verso: "DORIS BRY 510 EAST 86th ST. NEW YORK 28, N. Y." Handwritten on verso: "6-11", "BRY 2"
- Georgia O'Keeffe at Lake Powell, circa 1970s; 2006.6.889; Bry, Doris, 1920-2014; 1 Photographic Prints black and white photograph 7 15/16 x 10 inches; Handwritten on verso; Stamp of Doris Bry on versoStamp on verso: "DORIS BRY 510 EAST 86th ST. NEW YORK 28, N. Y." Handwritten on verso: "7-2", "BRY 3"
- Georgia O'Keeffe at Lake Powell, circa 1970s; 2006.6.890; Bry, Doris, 1920-2014; 1 Photographic Prints black and white photograph 7 15/16 x 10 inches; Handwritten on verso; Stamp of Doris Bry on versoStamp on verso: "DORIS BRY 510 EAST 86th ST. NEW YORK 28, N. Y." Handwritten on verso: "7-3", "BRY 4"
- Georgia O'Keeffe at Lake Powell, circa 1970s; 2006.6.891; Bry, Doris, 1920-2014; 1 Photographic Prints black and white photograph 7 15/16 x 10 inches; Handwritten on verso; Stamp of Doris Bry on versoStamp on verso: "DORIS BRY 510 EAST 86th ST. NEW YORK 28, N. Y." Handwritten on verso: "6-19", "BRY 5"
- Georgia O'Keeffe at Lake Powell, circa 1970s; 2006.6.892; Bry, Doris, 1920-2014; 1 Photographic Prints black and white photograph 7 15/16 x 10 inches; Handwritten on verso; Stamp of Doris Bry on versoStamp on verso: "DORIS BRY 510 EAST 86th ST. NEW YORK 28, N. Y." Handwritten on verso: "6-11", "BRY 6"
- Georgia O'Keeffe at Lake Powell, circa 1970s; 2006.6.893; Bry, Doris, 1920-2014; 1 Photographic Prints black and white photograph 7 15/16 x 10 inches; Handwritten on verso; Stamp of Doris Bry on versoStamp on verso: "DORIS BRY 510 EAST 86th ST. NEW YORK 28, N. Y." Handwritten on verso: "6-16", "BRY 7"
- Georgia O'Keeffe at Lake Powell, circa 1970s; 2006.6.894; Bry, Doris, 1920-2014; 1 Photographic Prints black and white photograph 7 15/16 x 9 15/16 inches; Handwritten on verso; Stamp of Doris Bry on versoStamp on verso: "DORIS BRY 510 EAST 86th ST. NEW YORK 28, N. Y." Handwritten on verso: "6-3", "BRY 8"
- Georgia O'Keeffe at Lake Powell, circa 1970s; 2006.6.895; Bry, Doris, 1920-2014; 1 Photographic Prints black and white photograph 8 x 9 15/16 inches; Handwritten on verso; Stamp of Doris Bry on versoStamp on verso: "DORIS BRY 510 EAST 86th ST. NEW YORK 28, N. Y." Handwritten on verso: "11-19", "BRY 10"
- Georgia O'Keeffe at Lake Powell, circa 1970s; 2006.6.896; Bry, Doris, 1920-2014; 1 Photographic Prints black and white photograph 7 15/16 x 10 inches; Handwritten on verso; Stamp of Doris Bry on versoStamp on verso: "DORIS BRY 510 EAST 86th ST. NEW YORK 28, N. Y." Handwritten on verso: "11-11", "BRY 11"
- Georgia O'Keeffe at Lake Powell, circa 1970s; 2006.6.897; Bry, Doris, 1920-2014; 1 Photographic Prints black and white photograph 9 7/8 x 8 1/16 inches; Handwritten on verso; Stamp of Doris Bry on versoStamp on verso: "DORIS BRY 510 EAST 86th ST. NEW YORK 28, N. Y." Handwritten on verso: "5-4", "BRY 12"
- Georgia O'Keeffe at Lake Powell, circa 1970s; 2006.6.898; Bry, Doris, 1920-2014; 1 Photographic Prints black and white photograph 7 15/16 x 10 inches; Handwritten on verso; Stamp of Doris Bry on versoStamp on verso: "DORIS BRY 510 EAST 86th ST. NEW YORK 28, N. Y." Handwritten on verso: "6-4", "BRY 13"
- Georgia O'Keeffe at Lake Powell, circa 1970s; 2006.6.899; Bry, Doris, 1920-2014; 1 Photographic Prints black and white photograph 7 15/16 x 10 inches; Handwritten on verso; Stamp of Doris Bry on versoStamp on verso: "DORIS BRY 510 EAST 86th ST. NEW YORK 28, N. Y." Handwritten on verso: "5-18", "BRY 14"
- Georgia O'Keeffe at Lake Powell, circa 1970s; 2006.6.900; Bry, Doris, 1920-2014; 1 Photographic Prints black and white photograph 7 15/16 x 9 15/16 inches; Handwritten on verso; Stamp of Doris Bry on versoStamp on verso: "DORIS BRY 510 EAST 86th ST. NEW YORK 28, N. Y." Handwritten on verso: "5-15", "BRY 15"
- Georgia O'Keeffe at Lake Powell, circa 1970s; 2006.6.901; Bry, Doris, 1920-2014; 1 Photographic Prints black and white photograph 9 7/8 x 8 1/16 inches; Handwritten on verso; Stamp of Doris Bry on versoStamp on verso: "DORIS BRY 510 EAST 86th ST. NEW YORK 28, N. Y." Handwritten on verso: "5-14", "BRY 16"
- Georgia O'Keeffe at Lake Powell, circa 1970s; 2006.6.902; Bry, Doris, 1920-2014; 1 Photographic Prints black and white photograph 7 15/16 x 9 15/16 inches; Handwritten on verso; Stamp of Doris Bry on versoStamp on verso: "DORIS BRY 510 EAST 86th ST. NEW YORK 28, N. Y." Handwritten on verso: "6-14", "BRY 17"
- Georgia O'Keeffe at Lake Powell, circa 1970s; 2006.6.903; Bry, Doris, 1920-2014; 1 Photographic Prints black and white photograph 9 7/8 x 8 1/16 inches; Handwritten on verso; Stamp of Doris Bry on versoStamp on verso: "DORIS BRY 510 EAST 86th ST. NEW YORK 28, N. Y." Handwritten on verso: "4-15", "BRY 18"
- Georgia O'Keeffe at Lake Powell, circa 1970s; 2006.6.904; Bry, Doris, 1920-2014; 1 Photographic Prints black and white photograph 7 15/16 x 10 inches; Handwritten on verso; Stamp of Doris Bry on versoStamp on verso: "DORIS BRY 510 EAST 86th ST. NEW YORK 28, N. Y." Handwritten on verso: "11-4", "BRY 19"
- Georgia O'Keeffe at Lake Powell, circa 1970s; 2006.6.905; Bry, Doris, 1920-2014; 1 Photographic Prints black and white photograph 7 15/16 x 9 15/16 inches; Handwritten on verso; Stamp of Doris Bry on versoStamp on verso: "DORIS BRY 510 EAST 86th ST. NEW YORK 28, N. Y." Handwritten on verso: "11-8", "BRY 20"
- Georgia O'Keeffe at Lake Powell, circa 1970s; 2006.6.906; Bry, Doris, 1920-2014; 1 Photographic Prints black and white photograph 7 15/16 x 10 inches; Handwritten on verso; Stamp of Doris Bry on versoStamp on verso: "DORIS BRY 510 EAST 86th ST. NEW YORK 28, N. Y." Handwritten on verso: "4-3", "BRY 21"
- Georgia O'Keeffe at Lake Powell, circa 1970s; 2006.6.907; Bry, Doris, 1920-2014; 1 Photographic Prints black and white photograph 7 15/16 x 9 15/16 inches; Handwritten on verso; Stamp of Doris Bry on versoStamp on verso: "DORIS BRY 510 EAST 86th ST. NEW YORK 28, N. Y." Handwritten on verso: "4-2", "BRY 22"
- Georgia O'Keeffe at Lake Powell, circa 1970s; 2006.6.908; Bry, Doris, 1920-2014; 1 Photographic Prints black and white photograph 7 15/16 x 9 15/16 inches; Handwritten on verso; Stamp of Doris Bry on versoStamp on verso: "DORIS BRY 510 EAST 86th ST. NEW YORK 28, N. Y." Handwritten on verso: "6-2", "BRY 9"
- Georgia OKeeffe with Olga and Joseph Hirshhorn, Early 1970s; 2006.6.909; Bry, Doris, 1920-2014; 1 Photographic Prints black and white photograph 9 7/8 x 8 inches; Handwritten on verso; Stamp of Doris Bry on verso; Bo II and Chia IIStamp on verso: "MAY NOT BE USED WITHOUT PERMISSION OF", "DORIS BRY 510 EAST 86th ST. NEW YORK 28, N. Y." (repeated 2x) Handwritten on verso: "22980-33"
- Georgia OKeeffe with Joseph Hirshhorn, Early 1970s; 2006.6.910; Bry, Doris, 1920-2014; 1 Photographic Prints black and white photograph 9 7/8 x 8 1/16 inches; Handwritten on verso; Stamp of Doris Bry on versoStamp on verso: "MAY NOT BE USED WITHOUT PERMISSION OF", "DORIS BRY 510 EAST 86th ST. NEW YORK 28, N. Y." (repeated 3x) Handwritten on verso: "22980-29"
- Olga Hirshhorn in Abiquiu, Early 1970s; 2006.6.911; Bry, Doris, 1920-2014; 1 Photographic Prints black and white photograph 9 7/8 x 8 1/16 inches; Handwritten on verso; Stamp of Doris Bry on versoStamp on verso: "MAY NOT BE USED WITHOUT PERMISSION OF", "DORIS BRY 510 EAST 86th ST. NEW YORK 28, N. Y." Handwritten on verso: "22980-33"
- Georgia O'Keeffe Walking with Olga and Joseph Hirshhorn, Early 1970s; 2006.6.912; Bry, Doris, 1920-2014; 1 Photographic Prints black and white photograph 7 15/16 x 10 inches; Handwritten on verso; Stamp of Doris Bry on versoStamp on verso: "MAY NOT BE USED WITHOUT PERMISSION OF", "DORIS BRY 510 EAST 86th ST. NEW YORK 28, N. Y." Handwritten on verso: "22980-22"
- Georgia O'Keeffe on walk with Olga and Joseph Hirshhorn, Early 1970s; 2006.6.913; Bry, Doris, 1920-2014; 1 Photographic Prints black and white photograph 7 15/16 x 10 inches; Handwritten on verso; Stamp of Doris Bry on versoStamp on verso: "MAY NOT BE USED WITHOUT PERMISSION OF", "DORIS BRY 510 EAST 86th ST. NEW YORK 28, N. Y." Handwritten on verso: "22980-21"
- Georgia O'Keeffe with Joseph Hirshhorn, Early 1970s; 2006.6.914; Bry, Doris, 1920-2014; 1 Photographic Prints black and white photograph 9 7/8 x 8 1/16 inches; Handwritten on verso; Stamp of Doris Bry on versoStamp on verso: "MAY NOT BE USED WITHOUT PERMISSION OF", "DORIS BRY 510 EAST 86th ST. NEW YORK 28, N. Y." Handwritten on verso: "22980-17"
- Georgia O'Keeffe with Joseph Hirshhorn, Early 1970s; 2006.6.915; Bry, Doris, 1920-2014; 1 Photographic Prints black and white photograph 7 15/16 x 10 inches; Handwritten on verso; Stamp of Doris Bry on versoStamp on verso: "MAY NOT BE USED WITHOUT PERMISSION OF", "DORIS BRY 510 EAST 86th ST. NEW YORK 28, N. Y." (repeated 2x) Handwritten on verso: "22980-12"